Trevor Jex

Software Engineer

Trevor Jex

5568 W 10080 N Highland, UT 84003

801-822-1805 jextrevor@gmail.com https://jextrevor.github.io

Skills

Extensive programming experience in Python, HTML, CSS, and Javascript (experience with React, Node.JS and websockets), with limited experience in C#, PHP, MySQL, and Java. Significant experience with Linux and Git. Non-exhaustive list of projects available at https://jextrevor.github.io.

Experience

- 1st Place Computer Science Award in 2016 Central Utah STEM Fair
- Technology Student Association 2015-17
- Plethora of personal projects (list available at https://jextrevor.github.io)

Work

Whistle Wok / Cashier, Server

AUGUST 2015 - PRESENT, AMERICAN FORK UT

Responsibilities include working quickly and effectively, greeting and working with people, and rapid decision-making.

Education

American Fork High School

AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2018, AMERICAN FORK UT

Top 5% of graduating class, cumulative 4.0 GPA and 5 AP classes, member of Chamber Choir and Chamber Orchestra, 2018 Department Choice for Performing Arts, President of Latin Club 2017-18, Treasurer of Inter-Club Council 2017-18.

Brigham Young University

AUGUST 2018, PROVO UT

Majoring in Computer Science.

References

Chris Crump / LDS Youth Leader 801-369-7092

chriscrump44@yahoo.com

Laurel Shelley / Latin Teacher

801-372-0551 ltshelley@gmail.com